thecoolgadgets.com 2019-11-19

# Privacy | Men's Gear

### PRIVACY POLICY

 **What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

 **What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: – To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) – To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you) – To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs) – To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature – To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.

 **How do we protect your information?**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

 **Do we use cookies?**  
Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Display Ads**

The Website uses Mediavine to manage all third-party advertising on the Website. Mediavine serves content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies. Mediavine may collect IP addresses and location to serve personalized ads.  If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices to opt-in or opt-out of this data collection, please visit <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

 **Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

 **Advertising**

Men’s Gear advertisers may engage in the collection of non-personally identifiable information about end users by third parties through the use of cookies and pixel tags. You can opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link located at <https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

Men’s Gear does not accept gifts, products or any other perks in exchange for posts. Any products we receive for review are only featured if we decide they have met our editorial standards.

Any advertising is clearly indicated as such, by being indicated with the word “Partner”, “Sponsored Post” (or similar wording).

From time to time, we feature giveaways, in which prizes are provided in consideration for a post on the site. The said prizes must meet our criteria.

Men’s Gear maintains affiliate relationships with trusted online stores. These links allow us to earn a small commission on the sale of products. Products are featured only because they meet editorial standards. We currently have an affiliate relationship with several stores including Amazon, Huckberry, and Kickstarter. Please feel free to [contact us](https://mensgear.net/contact) if you have any questions regarding this privacy policy.
